Inventory of the Devin A. Garrity papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Authors File, 1912-1981
  - Laura Helmer ed., You Can Survive the Atom Bomb, 1951 May-1951 August (Box-folder 12: 8)
    Includes manuscript, illustrations, and correspondence.
  - Karl Hess, None Dare Call It Capitalism, 1976 May-June (Box-folder 39: 21)
    Includes correspondence and outline.
  - Kathleen Hoagland, "The Old Castle Garden,", 1934 March-1948 April (Box-folder 10: 6)
    Includes correspondence and book review lists.
  - Kathleen Hoagland, 1000 Years of Irish Poetry, 1939 September-1952 February (Box-folder 11: 6)
  - Morris Horton, Power, 1972 February (Box-folder 17: 7-8)
  - Sisley Huddleston, France: The Tragic Years 1939-1947, 1955 May-1965 July (Box-folder 31: 5)
    Includes reviews, clippings, and correspondence.
  - Sisley Huddleston, The Enigma of a Virgin Queen, 1969 October (Box-folder 47: 5-6)
  - Frank Hughes, Your Little Red High School Our Little Red High School, 1951 November-1952 June (Box-folder 12: 9)
    Includes manuscript, correspondence, and pamphlet.
  - Frazier Hunt, The Untold Story of MacArthur, 1954 February-December (Box-folder 36: 6)
    Includes correspondence, newsletters, and clippings.
  - Frazier Hunt, The Untold Story of MacArthur, 1954 September-1955 April (Box-folder 31: 2)
    Includes clippings, reviews, and advertisements.
  - George B. de Huszar, Saving American Liberalism, 1950 February-1954 January (Box-folder 11: 4)
    Includes correspondence, press releases, and articles.
  - Commander Elmo H. Hutchinson, Violent Truce, 1955 November-1959 June (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - Commander Elmo H. Hutchinson, Violent Truce, 1956-1958 December (Box-folder 30: 5)
  - Dorothea Jones, Arthritis Cook Book, 1961 March-1966 October (Box-folder 5: 2)
    Includes articles, correspondence, and excerpt from manuscript.
  - William Kehoe, Enjoying Ireland, 1966 November-1981 November (Box-folder 38: 7)
    Includes correspondence, clippings, and index.
  - Robert Kendall, White Teacher, 1963 July-1968 February (Box-folder 30: 22)
    Includes clippings, articles, and summaries.
  - Robert Kephart, Human Events and Books For Libertarians, 1974 December-1975 March (Box-folder 49: 2)
    Includes correspondence and reviews.
  - Hyong W. Kim, The Storm Returning, 1975 June (Box-folder 9: 5)
  - Russell Kirk, Intelligent Women's Guide to Conservatism, 1960 January-1963 November (Box-folder 30: 26)
  - Frank L. Kluckhohn, Lyndon's Legacy, 1963 December-1968 May (Box-folder 30: 27)
    Includes clippings, reviews, and newsletters.
  - Alice Knight, 1972 June-1977 April (Box-folder 38: 8)
  - Alberta Lachicotte, Rebel Senator, 1966 October (Box-folder 30: 19)
    Includes a press release.
  - Richard Landells, Don Judas, undated (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - J.M. Larkman trans., Theory of Subversive Action, 1968 (Box-folder 10: 9)
  - William LaVarre, 1968 June (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Dell Leonardi, The Reincarnation of John Wilkes Booth, 1975 (Box-folder 34: 1-2)
    Includes manuscript and notes.
  - Arthur Liebman, Jews and the Left, 1979 (Box-folder 33: 3-5)
  - Alfred M. Lilienthal, Other Side of the Coin, 1955 February-1967 December (Box-folder 29: 14)
    Includes reviews, press releases, and general correspondence.
  - Alfred M. Lilienthal, Other Side of the Coin, 1964 October-1965 October (Box-folder 24: 4)
    Includes general correspondence.
  - Alfred M. Lilienthal, There Goes the Middle East, 1954 April-1962 October (Box-folder 30: 20)
    Includes newsletters, book summaries, and clippings.
  - Alfred M. Lilienthal, What Price Israel?, 1954 February-1965 July (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - James L. Lincoln, New Approaches to Industrial Economics, 1961 November-1965 June (Box-folder 29: 13)
    Includes reviews, articles, and funeral program.
  - Van Sinderen Lindsley, Jr., Not To Be Repeated, undated (Box-folder 42: 4)
  - Audrey W. Lloyd, The Untold Story of Jean Laffite, undated (Box-folder 5: 4)
    Includes clippings, correspondence, photographs, and manuscript.
  - Stephen D. Lockey, Sensitivity Drug Reactions, 1970 November-December (Box-folder 4: 7)
    Includes abstract, correspondence, and notes.
  - Ted Loefflar, 1967 March-December (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Dwight Macdonald and Donald Attwater, Modern Christians, 1947 April-July (Box-folder 36: 2)
  - Gary MacEoin and Akos Zombory, The Communist War On Religion, 1953 January-1965 July (Box-folder 29: 15)
    Includes articles and pamphlets.
  - Josef Mackiewicz, Victory of Provocation, 1970 January-1971 February (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Patrick Mahony, 1968 August-1971 February (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - Clarence Manion, The Conservative America, 1964 June-November (Box-folder 30: 17)
    Includes newsletters, clippings, and correspondence.
  - James J. Martin, American Liberalism & World Politics, 1965 February-May (Box-folder 30: 6)
    Includes reviews and correspondence.
  - John Martino, I Was Castro's Prisoner, 1963 September-1965 October (Box-folder 30: 2)
    Includes clippings and reviews.
  - Joe McCarthy, McCarthyism: The Fight for America, 1952 (Box-folder 43: 2)
  - W.H. McComb, The Business Man Must Save Himself, 1954 (Box-folder 46: 11)
    Includes book.
  - Albert W. McWhorter, It Did Happen Here, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 45: 4-5)
  - Samuel Menashe, The Bare Tree, undated (Box-folder 9: 4)
  - Lucille Miller, Lovely Land, 1955 May (Box-folder 46: 9)
  - Lorraine Moffet and Darcea Schiel, Health and Beauty Guide With Recipes By the Stars, 1967 May-October (Box-folder 27: 3)
  - John F. Montgomery, Hungary, The Unwilling Satellite, 1949 April (Box-folder 30: 3)
    Includes reviews, newsletters, and clippings.
  - John F. Montgomery, 1947 September-1950 January (Box-folder 46: 7)
    Includes clippings and maps.
  - Robert H. Montgomery, Sacco-Vanzetti: The Murder and the Myth, 1960 July-1961 October (Box-folder 30: 1)
  - George Morgenstern, Pearl Harbor, 1940 November-1954 September (Box-folder 30: 23)
    Includes articles, clippings, and advertisements.
  - Val Mulkerns, The World of Stone, 1951 November-1953 September (Box-folder 50: 9)
    Includes correspondence, advertisements, and articles.
  - Catherine A. Murphy and Leslie D. Weatherhead, "The Priest and the Community in the Stories of Frank O'Connor" and "The Case for Reincarnation,", 1961 (Box-folder 37: 1)
    Includes manuscripts.
  - Francis Neilson, The Crime, the Last Mile, Procession, 1955 April (Box-folder 12: 1)
    Includes pamphlets, reviews, and abstracts.
  - Jane S. Nickerson, North Africa Today, 1972 (Box-folder 4: 4)
    Includes excerpt from manuscript.
  - Jane S. Nickerson, Short History of South Africa, 1962 February (Box-folder 30: 25)
    Includes reviews and articles.
  - John H. Noble, I Was a Slave in Russia, 1956-1960 June (Box-folder 30: 28)
    Includes articles and clippings.
  - John H. Noble, I Was a Slave In Russia, 1956 January-1959 December (Box-folder 50: 8)
    Includes correspondence and advertisements.
  - Suza Norton, "Yoga,", 1976 May-1980 November (Box-folder 38: 21)
    Includes correspondence and a newspaper clipping.
  - Thomas J. Norton, Undermining the Constitution, 1951 March-April (Box-folder 30: 14)
    Includes reviews, clippings, and newsletters.
  - Liam O'Flaherty, Two Lovely Beasts, 1950 July-December (Box-folder 4: 1)
    Includes reviews, newspaper clippings, and correspondence.
  - Alexandra Oliver, Charles C. O'Connell, Ivan Obrenovich, et. al., 1961 August-1963 July (Box-folder 18: 4)
  - George H. Olmstead, Bayonets & Daisies: The Military Response to Revolution in America, 1972 May (Box-folder 9: 6-7)
  - John Ott, Health and Light, 1977 September-1980 September (Box-folder 38: 24)
    Includes correspondence, articles, and manuscript.
  - Gordon Palmer, By Freedom's Holy Light, 1964 December (Box-folder 30: 15)
    Includes reviews and press releases.
  - Alvah Peterson, Biological Control of Insects, 1958 January-1957 October (Box-folder 50: 4)
    Includes correspondence and introduction.
  - Elmer T. Peterson, Big Dam Foolishness, 1954 December-1966 March (Box-folder 30: 12)
    Includes reviews, newsletters, and correspondence.
  - Rudy Hart Phillips, Goodbye Latin America, 1976 May-1978 August (Box-folder 49: 15)
    Includes correspondence, reviews, and clippings.
  - Lionel Picton, Nutrition & the Soil, 1949 May-July (Box-folder 3: 5)
    Includes reviews and newspaper clippings.
  - J. Herculano Pires, Arigo, 1963 August-1966 December (Box-folder 43: 6)
    Includes manuscript, correspondence, and clippings.
  - John Powell, Bwana Reed, 1966-1968 May (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Katherine Proby, 1967 May (Box-folder 14: 26)
    Includes correspondence, photographs, and outlines.
  - Max Rafferty, On Education, 1968 October-November (Box-folder 30: 13)
  - Max Rafferty, Suffer Little Children, 1962 July-1965 (Box-folder 31: 27)
    Includes reviews, clippings, and pamphlets.
  - Richard S. Recker, Max Rafferty's Educational and Political Career in California, 1971 November-1972 February (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Douglas Reed, Battle for Rhodesia, 1967 March-1968 March (Box-folder 30: 4)
  - Douglas Reed, Somewhere South of Suez, 1951 March-1952 February (Box-folder 30: 9)
  - Tom A. Reedy, The German Story, 1951 November-1956 March (Box-folder 51: 21)
    Includes correspondence, outline, and clippings.
  - H.A. Reinhold, The Burden of Our Heritage, 1944 March-1946 November (Box-folder 18: 2-3)
    Includes correspondence, manuscript, and reviews.
  - Toby Rice, Africa: Dream or Nightmare?, 1970 August (Box-folder 8: 3-4)
  - Guy Richards, Imperial Agent, 1959-1967 July (Box-folder 30: 7)
    Includes reviews, correspondence, and clippings.
  - Ella Rigney, A Beginner's Book of Magic, 1963 June-1965 January (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Selden Rodman, 1959 April-1965 April (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - Grace Roosevelt, Memoirs, 1960 October-1964 June (Box-folder 33: 1-2)
  - E. Merrill Root, Brainwashing in the High Schools, 1957 March-1964 June (Box-folder 30: 8)
  - E. Merrill Root, Connecticut Yankee, Esquire: The Life and Times of Israel Putnam, 1962 October-1963 October (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - E.W. Russel, Jr., General Ironwood, 1970 January (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - Marjorie H. Russell, Glorious Presence, 1977 May-1978 February (Box-folder 37: 2)
    Includes correspondence and pamphlet.
  - Frank B. Salisbury, Wilderness Questions, 1972 August (Box-folder 42: 1)
  - Frederic R. Sanborn, Design for War, 1950 June-1956 June (Box-folder 30: 10)
  - Herbert R. Sass, Lord Shaftesbury's Darling, 1963 (Box-folder 9: 2-3)
  - Herbert R. Sass, 1955 July-1959 October (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - Fayez A. Sayegh, Arab Unity, 1957 July-1958 July (Box-folder 21: 6)
    Includes reviews, correspondence, and photographs.
  - Fayez A. Sayegh, Arab Unity, 1956 June-1958 October (Box-folder 30: 11)
  - Phyllis Schlafly, Strike From Space, 1965 November-1966 March (Box-folder 30: 16)
    Includes reviews, articles, and clippings.
  - Geroge Schuyler, The Future of the American Negro: A Symposium, 1965 March-1968 March (Box-folder 10: 3)
    Includes correspondence, newspaper clippings, and articles.
  - George Schuyler, The Future of the American Negro: A Symposium, 1965 June-1968 June (Box-folder 11: 7-8)
    Includes manuscript, articles, and correspondence.
  - Philippa Schuyler, Who Killed the Congo?, 1957-1967 May (Box-folder 30: 18)
    Includes reviews, press releases, and clippings.
  - Arthur Sheehan, Reincarnation of John Wilkes Booth, 1972 April (Box-folder 42: 3-5)
    Includes manuscript, correspondence, and historical documents.
  - Alexander R. Skutch, The Birds of Central America, 1963 September-October (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Robert J. Smith, Earth's Resources: Private Ownership vs. Public Waste, 1979 (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Boris Sokoloff, The White Nights, 1956 September-1968 January (Box-folder 31: 22)
    Includes press releases and advertisements.
  - Boris Sokoloff, Vitality vs Middle Age, 1957 August-November (Box-folder 43: 3)
  - Boris Sokoloff, What Is Russian Communism?, 1961 December-1966 March (Box-folder 6: 1-2)
    Includes manuscript, correspondence, and a photograph.
  - James L. Swauger, A Dozen Domestic Insects, 1963 March-1964 May (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Charles C. Tansill, America Goes to War and Back Door to War, 1938 April-1952 May (Box-folder 34: 5)
    Includes newspaper clippings and reviews.
  - Charles C. Tansill, America and the Fight for Irish Freedom, 1957 October-December (Box-folder 31: 23)
    Includes reviews, clippings, and articles.
  - Charles C. Tansill, 1948 July-1981 November (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Ellen Tarry, So You Wonder How It Feels? (To Be A Negro), undated (Box-folder 19: 8)
    Includes manuscript and outline.
  - Bernardo Teixeira, Fabric of Terror, 1967 January-1968 February (Box-folder 31: 24)
    Includes correspondence, articles, and photographs.
  - Rear Admiral Robert Theobald, Final Secret of Pearl Harbor, 1954 April-1956 May (Box-folder 2: 1)
    Includes book reviews, correspondence, and newspaper clippings.
  - Rear Admiral Robert Theobald, Final Secret of Pearl Harbor, 1954 April-1959 November (Box-folder 31: 26)
    Includes clippings, correspondence, and reviews.
  - Edward Tomlinson, Look Southward Uncle, 1951 March-1959 July (Box-folder 31: 8)
  - Vincent Torlini, Some Thoughts on the Philosophy of Conflict, 1969 January (Box-folder 7: 3-4)
  - Gilbert M. Tucker, Your Money and What to Do With It, 1960 May (Box-folder 31: 10)
    Includes press releases and clippings.
  - Dean Turner, The Einstein Myth, 1978 (Box-folder 35: 8)
  - Dean Turner and Richard Hazelett ed., The Ives Papers and the Einstein Myth, 1978 (Box-folder 35: 9-10)
  - Dean Turner and Richard Hazelett ed., The Ives Papers and the Einstein Myth, 1979 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Dean Turner and Richard Hazelett, 1977 August-1981 January (Box-folder 37: 10)
  - Rena M. Vale, Garden Beyond the Dunes, 1965 November (Box-folder 45: 6)
  - Ebed Van der Vlugt, Asia Aflame: Communism in the East, 1953 August-1955 August (Box-folder 31: 20)
  - F.J.P. Veale, War Crimes Discreetly Veiled, April 1959-October 1960 (Box-folder 31: 17)
    Includes clippings, reviews, and a synopsis.
  - Luigi Villari, Italian Foreign Policy Under Mussolini, 1957 May-1958 May (Box-folder 31: 18)
    Includes clippings, correspondence, and articles.
  - W. H. Von Dreele, If Liberals Had Feathers, 1967 November (Box-folder 31: 15)
    Includes advertisements and correspondence.
  - Angelita Von Munchausen and Alden Stahr, 1958 August-1963 February (Box-folder 18: 5)
    Includes correspondence and photographs.
  - Jerry Voorhis, Out of Debt, Out of Danger, 1949 May-1953 December (Box-folder 31: 13)
    Includes reviews and related articles.
  - Geoffrey Wagner, The Dispossessed, 1956-1957 February (Box-folder 31: 14)
    Includes press releases, clippings, and advertisements.
  - Ernest Walen, Noted Guerrillas, 1963 (Box-folder 32: 1)
    Includes manuscripts and correspondence.
  - Thomas R. Waring, Jr. ed., The Way it Was in Charleston, 1979 (Box-folder 48: 9-10)
  - V. Orval Watts, The United Nations Planned Tyranny, 1951 October-1963 September (Box-folder 31: 19)
    Includes reviews, clippings, and order forms.
  - Ferris Weddle, Cougar, 1963 October (Box-folder 11: 1)
    Includes manuscript, correspondence, newsletters, and photographs.
  - Nathaniel Weyl, Red Star Over Cuba, 1960 November-1963 September (Box-folder 31: 9)
  - Leonoard Wickenden, Make Friends With Your Land, 1949 June-1950 February (Box-folder 3: 2)
  - William D. Workman, Case for the South, 1960 January-1962 October (Box-folder 30: 21)
  - Rene A. Wormser, Foundations, 1958 April-1959 June (Box-folder 31: 25)
  - Alfred M. de Zayas, Nemesis at Potsdam, 1974 August-1975 December (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - Unidentified author, Jane Bond, undated (Box-folder 42: 2)
  - Unidentified author, My Unknown Chum, October 1912-January 1924 (Box-folder 19: 6)
    Includes correspondence and book reviews.
  - Unidentified author, The Scientist and the UFO, undated (Box-folder 4: 6)
    Includes chapter one and bibliography.
  - Unidentified author, Short History of North Africa, 1971 June (Box-folder 4: 8)
    Includes revised second half of manuscript.
  - Unidentified author, Who Gets Epstein?, 1972 November (Box-folder 5: 5)
    Includes manuscript and editing notes.
- Devin-Adair Publishing File, 1929-1969
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Correspondence from authors, 1929 August-1966 December (Box-folder 21: 11)
  - Correspondence from authors, 1944 January-1968 October (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Financial records and loans, 1945 February (Box-folder 24: 9)
  - Assorted newspaper clippings, 1951 November (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - Correspondence and financial records, 1965 January-August (Box-folder 18: 7)
  - Book ideas, miscellaneous material, correspondence, clippings, and newsletters, 1965-1969 April (Box-folder 46: 3)
  - Manuscripts coming, correspondence, outlines, 1967 June-November (Box-folder 27: 2)
- Subject File, 1919-1980
  Arranged alphabetically by subject, and chronologically thereunder (with the exception of the General subseries, which is arranged alphabetically).
  - General
    - American youth, world events, and short stories, 1949 April-1954 December (Box-folder 22: 8)
      Includes articles, notes, and newspaper clippings.
    - Asian affairs and communism, 1953 June-1954 October (Box-folder 22: 5)
      Includes interview notes, correspondence, and newspaper clippings.
    - Cock fighting, 1941 September-1948 December (Box-folder 20: 6)
      Includes manuscripts, articles, and photographs.
    - Conspiracies, 1952 March-1970 January (Box-folder 19: 7)
      Includes correspondence, articles, and newspaper clippings.
    - Dominican Republic, 1955 July-1956 July (Box-folder 43: 10)
      Includes articles and reports.
    - Estonia manuscript, Project Iceberg, 1968 May-September (Box-folder 5: 1)
      Includes correspondence, pamphlet, and photograph.
    - General pamphlets and correspondence, 1947-1962 (Box-folder 32: 4)
    - Joseph Goebbels, Robert Ley, Albert Speer, et al., Adolf Hitler, 1931-1935: Pictures From the Life of the Führer, 1978 July (Box-folder 35: 7)
      Includes photographs, articles, and correspondence.
    - Iceland, nutrition, conservation, 1954 March-1974 December (Box-folder 20: 3)
      Includes correspondence, pamphlets, and newspaper clippings.
    - Italian foreign policy, Villari, 1954 April-1955 October (Box-folder 21: 5)
      Includes essays, newspaper clippings, and illustrations.
    - MacArthur and metric system, 1978 November-1979 January (Box-folder 46: 1)
      Includes correspondence, articles, and congressional report.
    - Medical, criminal, ecology, 1975 July-1976 May (Box-folder 22: 1)
      Includes notes, articles, and newspaper clippings.
    - "Material Not for Publication," talk in Texas, 1966 November (Box-folder 43: 9)
      Includes notes, articles, and clippings.
    - Maev McGarrity, 1963 July (Box-folder 51: 12)
      Includes court documents and correspondence.
    - Nehls & O'Connell, 1959 March-1967 April (Box-folder 14: 8-9)
      Includes correspondence and financial records.
    - Quantrell, 1963 June-1967 April (Box-folder 43: 4-5)
      Includes correspondence, photographs, and clippings.
    - Dorothy Stock, 1958 May (Box-folder 47: 3)
      Includes sketches.
    - Villari advertising, 1957 January-1958 February (Box-folder 18: 9)
      Includes correspondence, newsletters, and advertising.
    - "Youth Action News,", 1973 September-1978 September (Box-folder 32: 2)
      Includes newsletters.
  - Africa
    - Conservation, 1964 December-1965 June (Box-folder 33: 8)
      Includes newspaper clippings, articles, and correspondence.
    - Rhodesia, 1965 April-1967 April (Box-folder 10: 1)
      Includes correspondence, newspaper clippings, and newsletters.
    - South Africa, 1965 February-March (Box-folder 21: 2)
      Includes newspaper clippings, correspondence, and essays.
    - South Africa, 1965 March-1973 February (Box-folder 23: 13)
      Includes articles and newsletters.
  - Economics and business
    - Business and world affairs, 1949 February-1956 February (Box-folder 22: 4)
      Includes articles, correspondence, and interview notes.
    - Economic wisdom, 1967 November-1974 December (Box-folder 31: 16)
      Includes articles, pamphlets, and correspondence.
    - Manufacturing, 1968 July-1970 May (Box-folder 48: 7)
      Includes samples, information, correspondence, and pamphlets.
  - Environment and conservation
    - "The Living Soil,", 1949 December-1951 June (Box-folder 23: 3-4)
    - Endangered animals, 1953 December-1974 March (Box-folder 12: 4)
      Includes assorted materials, articles, newsletters, and correspondence.
    - American Wildlife Institute, 1954 (Box-folder 17: 2)
      Includes notes, photographs, and articles.
    - Henry M. Hall, Shore Bird Correspondence, 1954 October-1960 December (Box-folder 10: 7)
      Includes articles, correspondence, and newspaper clippings.
    - Energy and environment, 1956-1975 April (Box-folder 22: 7)
    - Bird conservation, 1957 March-1980 November (Box-folder 20: 4-5)
    - The Nature Conservancy, 1958 September-1962 (Box-folder 12: 3)
      Includes correspondence, articles, and maps.
    - Conservation, 1959 August-1971 March (Box-folder 21: 10)
      Includes short stories, correspondence, and royalties.
    - Galapagos Logs, 1960 January-1964 March (Box-folder 17: 1)
      Includes correspondence and newspaper clippings.
    - Galapagos, 1960 October-1965 January (Box-folder 12: 10)
      Includes articles, photographs, and correspondence.
    - Environmental issues, general, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 12: 2)
      Includes pamphlets, articles, and newsletters.
    - Ecology, 1966 June-1968 August (Box-folder 21: 7)
      Includes articles, newspaper clippings, and pamphlets.
    - "The Mood of the Antarctic" and "Alaska 1968,", 1967 June-1969 January (Box-folder 17: 3)
      Includes essays, notes, and correspondence.
    - Statement of Fred S. Dubin before the Subcommittee on Energy of the House Science and Astronautics Committee, 1970 December-1973 September (Box-folder 21: 3)
    - Environmental issues, general, 1974 January (Box-folder 22: 2)
      Includes notes and articles.
  - Health and nutrition
    - Lee Foundation for Nutritional Research, 1944 April-1954 October (Box-folder 18: 1)
      Includes pamphlets and articles.
    - National Food Associates, ecological issues, 1969 November-1972 October (Box-folder 45: 5)
      Includes clippings, flyers, and correspondence.
    - National Health Federation, 1973 Convention, 1971-1973 November (Box-folder 33: 6)
      Includes correspondence, newsletters, and press releases.
    - National Food Associates, 1971 October-1974 February (Box-folder 23: 5-6)
      Includes correspondence, articles, and notes.
    - National Food Associates and cancer, 1972 April-1975 August (Box-folder 45: 7)
      Includes articles, clippings, and newsletters.
    - Natural food and cancer, 1975 December (Box-folder 35: 1)
    - Natural Food Associates (Nicholas, Lavin), 1976 February-November (Box-folder 38: 17)
  - Irish culture
    - Paul Vincent Carroll, Irish Short Stories and Plays, 1958 March-1961 December (Box-folder 51: 5)
      Includes correspondence, photographs, and sheet music.
    - Dermott MacManus, Irish Earth Folk, 1958 May-1962 January (Box-folder 51: 9)
  - Princeton University
    - Daily Review, Princeton Alumni Weekly, 1944 May-1973 March (Box-folder 44: 1)
    - Survey, 1948 May-1959 January
      - Faculty, 1948 May-1954 April (Box-folder 1: 11)
      - Economics, 1949 March-1953 April (Box-folder 1: 10)
      - Politics 203, 1949 November-1953 April (Box-folder 1: 9)
      - Duplicate materials, 1949 November-1953 April (Box-folder 1: 4)
      - Faculty duplicates, 1949 December-1959 January (Box-folder 1: 5)